<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ggplot2 on owenqi</title>
    <link>/tags/ggplot2/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Ggplot2 on owenqi</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 21 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/ggplot2/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Analysis on COVID-19 Vaccine in US</title>
      <link>/2021/05/21/analysis-on-covid-19-vaccine-in-us/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2021/05/21/analysis-on-covid-19-vaccine-in-us/</guid>
      <description>As I am going to get my first dose next week, I would like have some ideas about the safety of the vaccine. In Canada, AstraZeneca (AZ) and Pfizer are delivered. But recently, AZ are no longer suggested in province like Quebec and Ontario. I am going to use the available data on US.
Vaccination in USAnd vaccinations data are available on Our World in Data.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>COVID-19 in Quebec</title>
      <link>/2020/03/31/covid-19-in-quebec/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2020/03/31/covid-19-in-quebec/</guid>
      <description>Part 1, Written in MarchDue to my inexperience in maintaining Blogs via Github pages, each time I post a new post, the whole site will be rendered completely, some of my functions are not longer working due to the update format of the website, but I still leave this post as a note for my studies.
As the current COVID-19 situation in Canada, I am also forced to work from home.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bangladesh Ground Arsenic with R</title>
      <link>/2019/07/05/bangladesh-ground-arsenic-with-r/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2019/07/05/bangladesh-ground-arsenic-with-r/</guid>
      <description>This post demostrate implements the computation and visualization of CSI (Contamination Severity Index) develop by Dr. P.K Sen in 2016, data obtain from British Geological Survey.
Map getting from GADM version 2.8
load(&amp;#39;data.Rda&amp;#39;)thana_map &amp;lt;- readRDS(gzcon(url(&amp;#39;https://biogeo.ucdavis.edu/data/gadm2.8/rds/BGD_adm3.rds&amp;#39;)))1. ExpressionLet \(Y_{(i)}, i = 1,2, \ldots, n\) be the ordered sample from a region (can be division/district/thana), in our case, thana.
Let \(M\) denote the number of observation less than the threshold \(L\) (given).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Plot Area Under the Curve with ggplot2</title>
      <link>/2019/03/05/plot-area-under-the-curve-with-ggplot2/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2019/03/05/plot-area-under-the-curve-with-ggplot2/</guid>
      <description>This is a very short post for a summary of the blog post, I will make a quick function for myself to graph some area under the curve for convenience.
Create your own functionIf like well-known curve, it is already defined in R such as dnorm, otherwise you can define your own function.For simplicity, I will only use standard normal (dnorm) (may update in the future).</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>