<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on owenqi</title>
    <link>/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on owenqi</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 18 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>EDA on Bangladesh Groundwater Arsenic Part 2</title>
      <link>/2019/02/18/eda-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2019/02/18/eda-2/</guid>
      <description>We have perfrom initial EDA on arsenic level in the early post. From the plots in part 1
The region being chosen there doesn’t seem to be much spatial correlationIt is hard to interpret this in longitude and latitudeIn this post, R code for simple data transformation and technique use in part 1 will NOT be shown again, we just present the result. Code for new technique will be included.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EDA on Bangladesh Groundwater Arsenic Part 1</title>
      <link>/2019/02/08/eda/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2019/02/08/eda/</guid>
      <description>This post is a practice note based on tutorials from tutorial 1, tutorial 2 and tutorial 3 towards my thesis, we first perform EDA on data of original scale, once we have idea about our data, we may further perform kriging.
Data was downloaded from British Geological Survey as “DPHE/BGS National Hydrochemical Survey”, describing various groundwater quality parameters for several thousand wells measured by the British Geological Survey throughout Bangladesh in 1998-1999.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>An R Markdown Examples</title>
      <link>/2019/02/07/rmd-example/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2019/02/07/rmd-example/</guid>
      <description>This post is mainly use for examine the rendering of the theme of the blog. The main aspect that I am care about is the support and hightlight of common use programming languages in this blog such as R and Python, some of the R code I put in this post are simple and non-informative.
R StudioTo work with R and R Markdown, for starters,
Install RInstall the lastest version of RStudioInstall knitr package using install.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>