<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>R on owenqi</title>
    <link>/tags/r/</link>
    <description>Recent content in R on owenqi</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 31 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/r/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>COVID 19 in Quebec</title>
      <link>/2020/03/31/covid-19-in-quebec/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2020/03/31/covid-19-in-quebec/</guid>
      <description>As the current COVID-19 situation in Canada, I am also forced to work from home. During the weekend, I try to learn some stuff for fun. This post will illustrate the map reflecting the COVID-19 count in Quebec.
To obtain the data, we first scrape the information from the goverment’s website Quebec.ca, who provides daily updates upto the Administrative Region level. This time I will use rvest to grab the information.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Estimating scale and correlation parameters for GEE</title>
      <link>/2019/11/25/estimating-scale-and-correlation-parameters-for-gee/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2019/11/25/estimating-scale-and-correlation-parameters-for-gee/</guid>
      <description>This is a recall for some of what I have learned last year (2018, Fall). Back then, the main focus was on Bayesian models. A friend asked me a question few days ago on estimating the parameters related to Generalized Estimating Equation (GEE). In general, this can be comfortably handeled by the R package such as geepack, but she wanted to know the exact estimation procedures. Hence, I review some of my materials, and a book recommended by my colleague which will be referenced in the end.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bangladesh Ground Arsenic with R</title>
      <link>/2019/07/05/bangladesh-ground-arsenic-with-r/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2019/07/05/bangladesh-ground-arsenic-with-r/</guid>
      <description>This post demostrate implements the computation and visualization of CSI (Contamination Severity Index) develop by Dr. P.K Sen in 2016, data obtain from British Geological Survey.
Map getting from GADM version 2.8
load(&amp;#39;data.Rda&amp;#39;)thana_map &amp;lt;- readRDS(gzcon(url(&amp;#39;https://biogeo.ucdavis.edu/data/gadm2.8/rds/BGD_adm3.rds&amp;#39;)))1. ExpressionLet \(Y_{(i)}, i = 1,2, \ldots, n\) be the ordered sample from a region (can be division/district/thana), in our case, thana.
Let \(M\) denote the number of observation less than the threshold \(L\) (given).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Plot Area Under the Curve with ggplot2</title>
      <link>/2019/03/05/plot-area-under-the-curve-with-ggplot2/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2019/03/05/plot-area-under-the-curve-with-ggplot2/</guid>
      <description>This is a very short post for a summary of the blog post, I will make a quick function for myself to graph some area under the curve for convenience.
Create your own functionIf like well-known curve, it is already defined in R such as dnorm, otherwise you can define your own function.For simplicity, I will only use standard normal (dnorm) (may update in the future).</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>